Hassan Taiwo

Front-end Developer

Personal Info

Phone

+2348100870577

Email

alhassansahih@gmail.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/weirdhassan

Github

github.com/im-hassan-wd

Skills

HTML

CSS

Bootstrap

JavaScript

PHP



GraphGL

Language

English

I'm Hassan T. Weird, an african born, seasoned in web development and user-interface designing. Using my creativity to bring ideas to life. I'm not an expert in my field but I'm trying so hard to be one. I have a proficiency in programmming languages and frameworks like Html, Css, JavaScript, Bootstrap . I also have pretty vague idea on graphQL and Php. I love to develop new user-intefacing features, write neat and reuseable code. I'm motivated by meeting set targets within deadlines, as it gives me a sense of accomplishments and it's something I can look on and say 'I achieved that'.

EDUCATION

2020-01 - Student, Obafemi Awolowo University present Computer Engineering

Member of Student Association of Computer Technology. Worked on a student project to increase the speed of computer technologies.

EXPERIENCE

2021-06 - Side Hustle present Internship

Interact with customers by phone, email and inperson to provide information.

Analysed problems, Idetified solutions and made good decision.

Collaborated in professional team to solve workflow issues.

ACHIEVEMENT

2021-06 Jobberman Accelerated Soft Skill

Jobberman - Coursera

7UE6JCECDQB9